{
  "vessel" : "BOTTLE",
  "responses" : [
    {
      "question" : "questions_question7",
      "answer" : "spotify:track:6dgUya35uo964z7GZXM07g"
    },
    {
      "question" : "questions_question2",
      "answer" : "spotify:track:54X78diSLoUDI3joC2bjMz"
    },
    {
      "question" : "questions_question8",
      "answer" : "spotify:track:5Z2MiIZ5I3jJvvmeWMLbOQ"
    },
    {
      "question" : "questions_question10",
      "answer" : "spotify:track:2NFag2zEx2GC5ySs0d3IaS"
    },
    {
      "question" : "questions_question17",
      "answer" : "spotify:track:45S5WTQEGOB1VHr1Q4FuPl"
    },
    {
      "question" : "questions_question9",
      "answer" : "spotify:track:4y0bx3TIbkpd6IKfN0yrLC"
    },
    {
      "question" : "questions_question18",
      "answer" : "spotify:track:06cCziAHtDg6pcsidZHu03"
    },
    {
      "question" : "questions_question4",
      "answer" : "spotify:track:0W6I02J9xcqK8MtSeosEXb"
    },
    {
      "question" : "questions_question11",
      "answer" : "spotify:track:0Dl965SLJGi9bB0SrvtPRx"
    },
    {
      "question" : "questions_question19",
      "answer" : "spotify:track:14dJexYlvd3t3XAtD1pYW1"
    },
    {
      "question" : "questions_question16",
      "answer" : "spotify:track:0KOUhmRuztZUFOl6QCogLE"
    }
  ]
}